The next day
Yeah!
Touch?
Today is the event of Touch!
Yeah!
I'm wearing a knitwear of Onie today.
I can't see it because it's damaged.
I can't see it.
There is a button here.
I took it off and put it on like a
vest.
I'm going to change it.
I'm going to show you my clothes.
I usually wear a white T-shirt, but I'm
wearing a pink one.
I'm not sure if it looks good on me.
We'll do our best for the rehearsal!
It's already over.
It's already dark.
But it's a good feeling, isn't it?
It's warm.
I can see the smoke.
Please subscribe to our channel and
like us.
We'll be waiting for you as a guest.
Oh, really?
If you like it, please subscribe to our
channel.
If you have a plan, please let us know.
She's so funny.
Who is next to us?
It's Kanami.
It's Hanako.
Today, Hanako is going to be our guest.
Will she notice us?
Hello?
What?
Oh!
You look like a homeless.
We are here at the LUSSBAN TV.
Today, we are going to have a talk
about
the name of the show and
the theme of today's live show.
It's called Naked Dream.
No, no, no.
What? Is this broken?
It's broken.
Please say something to break it.
I'm sorry. Please break it.
Let's say it together.
I love you!
My hands are warm.
Bye-bye.
Good morning!
It's not up.
It's up.
I'll upload it.
I finished studying.
I'm good at it.
I'm good at it today.
My hands are wavering.
I want to sleep.
It wasn't sleep.
I'm sleepy.
It's live.
I'll do my best to give you a touch.
Kei-chan, please do that.
Today's eye ball.
Yes.
Touch!
Today's eye ball.
I don't know what to do.
I'll do my best.
I want to do it.
I'll do it twice.
I don't know.
I'll do it a lot.
Live!
Yes.
I'll do it live.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
Bathroom?
Bye bye.
High-five!
Good luck!
I'm going in!
Last training.
We will shoot are runaway paratroopers
to eliminate you
It's an electric fan filled with
cheating messages!
Yuuki and Heronsaka's проблем?
ん?
Thunder and Reckoning
I'm so excited about today's wherever
we go because we won't have any problem
with myself butwhatever
It's leaking.
What's going on?
I was filming.
It's leaking.
Why?
Please subscribe to my channel.
It's leaking.
It's a carbicom.
What?
It's not focusing.
I can't get it.
Look.
It's a mosquito.
I found it.
The camera is so beautiful.
I noticed today that there is only one
hole in the earphone of Jelly.
12 holes.
Aki, you have one too.
What?
Smile.
One.
I can't get it.
It's small.
Smiling.
I'm going to take a picture.
Bye bye!
I'm not good at it.
Let's go!
We've finished the practice.
Say I love you.
Wee!
Thank you for watching!
I bought a different eye drops today.
I'm glad.
Are you?
Yes.
I always use eye drops.
Thank you.
I'm a dry eye.
I'm using eye drops.
I'm a complex.
I'm a dry eye.
Glasses, color, contact.
What's that class?
I was asked what I do every day.
Glasses, color, contact.
I thought I had to say something to
each of you.
Glasses, color, contact.
Kabigon, Kabigon.
I heard that the action is like
Kabigon.
What is Kabigon's action?
Just eat and sleep.
Is that so?
I don't know much.
When I received the phone case of
Kabigon, I got a message that I received
it.
Did you get a message?
I wanted to say it to someone.
The home screen is a recording screen.
Kabigon is a live-streaming.
I'm addicted to it now.
It was interesting that it was not only
a case.
Is it cool?
It's cool.
The wind is good.
The water is good.
Stop it.
How is it?
Why don't you say anything?
Hey.
I always watch Tokibaro.
I only watch Tokibaro on YouTube.
It's hot.
I'm doing the same thing.
What about you, Hiyori?
I'll put it in my bag when I do the
same thing with Julia and Hito.
What did you do?
I don't know.
I did something with what I had.
I'll cool you down.
It's hot.
Is it right?
We have the same blood.
It's a miracle.
I want a big one.
A crane.
Yes, a crane.
I'm looking forward to your support.
Thank you.
We've got a lot of cameras.
Yes, we do.
There are so many.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11.
Thank you.
We're going to go on stage.
Bye-bye.
I think it's better to use your hands.
I think I can do it.
Do you use it?
Yes, I do.
We have 20 minutes left.
We have to do it.
I'll fix it.
Thank you for watching.
It's a little cold.
But it's a little amazing.
It's scary.
We will do our best.
Please watch our video.
The sound of a vacuum cleaner.
It's February today.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for watching.
What's the next birthday?
It's in September.
Let's say it.
It's a bit nostalgic.
I remember.
What's the next birthday?
It's a bit hard.
We have only 15 minutes left.
Really?
20 minutes?
I think so.
It's time for me to go.
Bye.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Today, I'm wearing pink makeup.
My eye shadow is pink, my lip color is
pink, and my blush is pink.
I've been into orange makeup for a
while, but I'm wearing pink makeup
recently.
Did you notice?
What color did you wear, Aki?
I'm wearing pink.
I heard that you said, pink day.
It's the same.
It's 5 minutes before the show starts.
I'll go to the stage.
Touch!
I'm going to do something interesting.
I'm wearing a perfume.
I'm doing a push-up.
Can you raise your leg?
Thank you.
I don't like it.
Can you raise your leg?
I'm doing a push-up.
I don't know.
Stop it.
You are embarrassing me.
I've never done a push-up.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for watching.
I can't do it.
Today, I was doing a story time.
I opened the July cider on YouTube.
I always open the July cider on
YouTube.
I'm late to talk, so I open it at 1.5
times or 1.5 times.
July cider.
You are fast.
I can't do it.
I want to do it.
You can do it.
That's good.
I'm going to watch it.
Bye-bye.
Please subscribe to our channel.
I love this so much!
I can't remember the gesture.
It's me.
4 minutes left.
The first part.
The second part.
Do you think my bangs look good today?
I don't know because it's dark.
I know.
Is it OK?
Yes.
Hello.
Everyone.
I'm Kanami.
I'm Julia.
I'm Hitoka.
I'm Haruka.
I'm Aki.
I'm Hiyori.
We are SAKIMI.
Rock on!
Thank you.
I'm Hitoka.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
Someone is touching me.
I want to touch everyone's heart.
The heart is here.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
I'm a little nervous.
Are you okay?
Please.
Endless.
Gamushara.
It's like a rainbow. It's beautiful.
The second day of the concert
It's good!
It's crumpled
No way!
Do you know?
Wow!
I'm fine
My bangs
Today's bangs
It's too early
I'm surprised by the time
Let's line up
The best order of life
The second day of the concert
The third day of the concert
The fourth day of the concert
Thank you!
Good work
Thank you very much!
It was fun, wasn't it?
High, high, high, high, high touch!
It was fun! It was fun!
Oh, no, the water is gone.
See you!
Thank you for your hard work!
It's over!
Thank you for watching!
Thank you!
It was a live that connected our
hearts.
Right?
It was connected!
It was really fun!
There were a lot of emotional songs.
I'm glad.
We were looking back on the past and
singing a miracle song.
When we were singing,
I was reminded of the old days.
It was fun to be reminded of the old
days.
I hope everyone will remember the old
days and enjoy today's live.
I'm glad.
It's over!
Thank you!
It was fun!
I'm glad that new memories are being
engraved in the old songs.
I hope that people who know Toki-chan
will make a lot of memories with
nostalgic songs.
I hope so.
Let's make a lot of exciting memories
with everyone!
Thank you!
See you!
Touch! Touch! Touch!
High! High! High! High! High Touch!
Bye!
Oh, Julia was filming us, so let's take
the video!
Shall we?
If you think this video is fun, or if
you feel good, or if you feel excited,
please subscribe to our channel and
give Julia a thumbs up!
Oh!
What are you doing?
What?
Julia, give her a thumbs up!
Give her a thumbs up!
Aki, give her a thumbs up!
Miya, and Tome, give her a thumbs up!
Please subscribe to our channel and
give us a thumbs up!
And leave us comments!
We read all the comments!
We read all the comments on YouTube and
in the chat!
Thank you!
We'll be looking for more fun videos!
That's right!
Bye!
Bye bye!
We finished the live!
We finished!
We were able to do the live
with our hearts!
We did it!
It was so fun!
I think the makeup artist
was able to tell
that everyone was having fun!
It was so fun!
It was a fun live!
It was fun!
The beauty was the best!
Yeah, the beauty!
It was fun!
It's been a while since we did
the old song,
but did you notice
that the first part
was a little bit
like an acrobat?
That was the original form,
but we were able to shake hands
and talk a little bit,
but we went back
and did it again
in the original form.
Did you notice?
We did!
It's good to be able to do
old songs and recent songs
and shake hands
with Inagana Yui-chan!
Yeah!
It was fun!
I hope we can connect
more and more people
with our songs,
so please continue
to support us!
I hope we can meet more people!
Thank you!
What?
I don't know!
I respect Hitoka.
It's good.
Hitoka, you're good.
I did it.
This live is relaxing before it starts.
Hiori is excited.
She's a little nervous.
But she's excited about today.
I don't know.
Sometimes it happens.
Sometimes it happens today.
Today, I was able to get in touch with
you.
We had eye contact.
We had eye contact a lot today.
We saw each other in places we don't
usually see.
I said it at the live.
I was singing a song.
I was looking at Hitoka and I felt her
expression.
I felt her expression when I was
looking at Hitoka.
I saw her and she was smiling.
I thought she did something.
I felt her expression.
I thought she was smiling because she
did something.
I thought she did something.
I was surprised.
I thought she was cute.
I think hearts are connected.
Heart to heart.
This live was heart to heart.
It's perfect.
It was a live that I thought was heart
to heart.
I was looking back at the old pictures.
I was emotional.
I was looking at the pictures of the
victory song.
I was looking at Hiori's face.
Stop it.
I was looking at her face.
It was a great live.
I think it was a really fun live.
I hope you think so.
Let's make a lot of memories and touch
a lot.
Finally,
High high high high high touch.
Bye bye.
How was it?
It was so fun.
It was fun.
I could relax and sing live.
I sang the old songs like Daijiman
Friends.
I sang the song of Oharu before Tokisen
was released.
I sang the original song.
I was surprised to see Oharu singing
the song in the lesson.
I couldn't remember it.
I couldn't remember it at all.
I remember the old songs and the
original songs.
It was a live performance that I could
look back on.
I felt like I was touching my old
heart.
I felt like I was closer to the
members.
I was in eye contact with them.
I was happy to see them.
I remember the second song of the song
called Jinsei Saikondo Melody.
I remember that.
I was the first to put my hand forward.
Hitoka was the same.
I was in front of her.
I was in a perfect circle.
I thought it was good to have a live
performance like this.
I wanted to have a live performance
like this.
We performed the song called Touch.
I heard that the theme was to touch and
meet.
We were conscious of that.
We performed the song called Touch.
We wanted to make the audience feel
this distance.
I thought so.
I enjoyed it.
I was glad that we could do a live
performance at home.
We don't usually jump at home.
We jumped at home.
I was surprised.
We jumped at home on New Year's Day.
That's good.
We could do a wave.
We could do it because of the camera
angle.
I think everyone jumped at the timing
they wanted.
I couldn't see it, but I could see it.
I know what you mean.
I could see that.
I like the lyrics of Beauty.
I like the lyrics.
I was about to say the same thing.
I like the lyrics of Rap.
I like the lyrics.
I think it's a good song.
I want to cherish this song.
It's an old song.
I want to make this song more popular.
I want to cherish the old songs and the
current songs.
Thank you for inviting us to your first
touch performance.
I'm glad.
I've never been to an event like this.
I'm glad to be invited to this event.
I think we've grown up since we were
young.
I want to use the word touch in the
future.
We want to meet a lot of people.
I think there will be a lot of live
performances this year.
I want to meet a lot of people in
various situations.
Thank you.
Touch.
See you again.
When you're lost, remember
So that you can laugh even when it
rains
Come on, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, I'm the same as
yesterday
The city after the rain is sparkling
My heart is like a sunny pattern
I play the piano of the rainbow
And play the piano of the rainbow
Goodbye, goodbye, I'm the same as
yesterday
The city after the rain is sparkling
My heart is like a sunny pattern
I play the piano of the rainbow
Please subscribe to our channel!